Heat.
Hey,
Is there going to now?
What are you doing?
I'm swimming.
Can you see what I'm doing right now?
>> She's just asking you. Can you answer it
properly? It's already 12:00 p.m. and
almost 1:00 a.m. You should get some
rest.
>> Yes, because I hear that obviously can
cause you sick. It's really important
for you to take care of yourself on
behalf.
Don't disturb me. Just mind your own
business.
See, I already told you already. Don't
just focus on studying and eat proply.
Now look, you're falling as sick.
>> I'm sorry, Mom, for causing you so much
trouble. But how we are going to pay the
hospital bills?
>> Lucky we have an insurance which is
potential insurance.
>> This insurance covers hospital bills
including pre and post hospital
treatment. Day surgery and emergency
treatment depending on the selected plan
and policy limits.
There are two ways hospital risk are
covered. First is cashless hospitalation
at penal hospitals. The policy holder
only needs to present their credential
medical card. The hospital will verify
the coverage and credential will pay the
hospital directly.
The patient only pays for expenses that
are not covered by the policy.
Why people who need protection have to
consider buying these policies? People
who need protection should consider
potential insurance. Life is full of
unexpected risk like illness, accidents,
disability or even death. Protential
provides comprehensive financial
protection when these things happen. It
helps cover medical expenses and
replaces lost income so families can
stay financially stable during tough
times. Potential also offers long-term
security and saving plans. This give
peace of mind and helps people plan for
the future while protecting their loved
ones. Next, I would like to explain the
exclusions of a potential insurance
policy. Policy expressions are
situations where the insurance company
will not pay a claim. For example,
credential does not cover pre-existing
illnesses, self-inflicted injuries, or
losses caused by illegal activities.
Claims related to alcohol or drug abuse
are also excluded. In addition, losses
caused by war, or dangerous activities
may not be covered. Therefore, it is
very important for policy holders to
read and understand their policy
execution before buying issuance.
Second is reimbursement for non-panel
hospitals. The patient pays the hospital
bill first and submits the medical
documents and received to predition.
Eligible expenses will then be reimbured
according to the policy terms. In
conclusion, potential medical insurance
help reduce the financial burden of
medical expenses and provides financial
protection and peace of mind.
Alhamdulillah, we already have
insurance. I promise I will take care of
myself starting from now. It's okay.
It's okay.
My mom